FABULUJE OLAMIDE CALEB

ADDRESS: 9, Maberu Street, Oraye Quarters, Ise - Ekiti, Ekiti State.

MOBILE: +234 8149 153 469

E-MAIL: horlerbammy@gmail.com

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

COMPUTER TECHNOLOGIST | NETWORK ENGINEER | BROADCAST ENGINEER

A solution driven system administrator and an expert with successful track record in implementing and supporting IT infrastructure, with multi-disciplinary skills in executing strategies and managing people to meet client's expectations.

Strategic specialist with a flair for adapting quickly to a dynamic, technical and quality focused environment.

Versatile, methodical and goal oriented with positive attitude.

EDUCATION	
Higher National Diploma in Computer Engineering Rufus Giwa Polytechnic, Owo, Ondo State.	2016 - 2019
National Diploma in Computer Engineering Rufus Giwa Polytechnic, Owo, Ondo State.	2013 2015
Secondary School Certificate Examination Success College, Ise – Ekiti, Ekiti State.	2004 2011
Primary School Leaving Certificate Berachah Children School, Ise – Ekiti, Ekiti State.	1998 - 2004

TECHNICAL COMPETENCIES

* Data center knowledge - Power (AC/DC), cooling, racking, cable management etc.

Network Monitoring using Solarwinds and PRTG NMS Tools.

Configuration and Integration of Newly deployed Links.

Setting up of DHCP/DNS Server (Cisco IOS and Windows Server platform).

Configuration of Cisco routers and switches.

Routing Protocol - RIPv2, EIGRP, OSPF, BGP, and equivalent IPv6 protocols.

Cisco ISE for Network access control.

ForeScoute for network access control.

Microsoft 2003/2007/2010 (PowerPoint, Outlook, Word, & Excel).

CCTV / Surveillance Monitoring - DVR, HVR and NVR.

Computer/Laptop repair and upgrade, (Software and hardware)

Setting up Live Streaming for Camcorders or IP Cameras using OBS & other streaming platforms

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Aug 17, 2020 - April 26, 2021

Planet Fm, 101.1 Uyo [Broadcasting/Media]

Planet Avenue, Ibiaku Uruan, Akwa Ibom State

HEAD OF ICT Core Duties

• Liaising with the Head of Engineering to proffer lasting solutions to ICT problems.

Ensuring downtime period are not unnecessarily too long Ensuring contingencies are in place in the event of downtime.

Ensuring communication channels are in good condition.

Ensuring no complete run out on IT network and their subscription.

Liaising with the social media officers to ensure live streaming at the stipulated time.

Maintaining logs and lead-time on subscription renewals.

Maintaining logging and maintenance report on IT Hardware

Ensuring no abuse on communication network e.g. internet usage.

Setting Limiting IDs to ensure no abuse.

Constantly reviewing and advising management on IT changes and upgrade to latest version.

Verifying all IT request and ensure they are in line with the business requirement.

Liaising with software and IT providers and ensure quality and standards are not compromise.

Carrying out routine maintenance checks on Hardware.

Ensuring set up, upgrade and maintenance of station website,

Keeping stocks and inventories of critical spares.

Any other assignments as maybe called upon by the Company.

Reporting to Head of Engineering/General Manager.

Jun 29, 2020 - Aug 17, 2020

Planet Fm, 101.1 Uyo [Broadcasting/Media

Planet Avenue, Ibiaku Uruan, Akwa Ibom State

TECHNICIAN Core Duties

Training and maintaining the day to day operations and to assume responsibility for maintaining generator sets, UPS, lightings, and fixtures, air-conditions etc.

Ensuring minimal/no downtime during transmission.

Carrying out troubleshooting when necessary.

- Responsible for the completion of all maintenance service request as assigned.
- Maintaining diesel consumption logging and calibrating.
- Monitoring of signal quality and strength.
- Operating, Maintaining, Updating and repairing equipment used at the station.
- Keeping abreast of constant changes in technology by investigating new systems, techniques and equipment.
- All other chores as may be directed by management or the Head of the department.
- Reporting to Head of Engineering.

Jun 2019 - Jun 2020 (NYSC)

Planet Fm, 101.1 Uyo [Broadcasting/Media]

Planet Avenue, Ibiaku Uruan, Akwa Ibom State

Core Duties

- Monitoring of signal quality and strength.
- Responsible for day to day operations of transmitter and studio's equipment.
- Maintaining broadcast automation systems for the studio and automatic transmission system for the transmitter plant.
- Ensure no downtime occurs during transmission and troubleshoot when necessary,
- Day-to-day logging of engineering activities.
- Inspection and testing of transmission equipment, repairs and maintenances of transmission systems.
- Ensure routine inspections of electrical equipment.
- Excellent knowledge and understanding of relevant IT facilities and Networking.
- Strong knowledge of office automation including the ability to install and troubleshoot Computer systems.
- Vast Knowledge in Systems' Hardware, Software and Firmware Troubleshooting.
- Swift response to all troubleshooting calls and all engineering faults/issues.
- Perfect Live streaming with Video Camcorders or IP Cameras.
- Proper Knowledge in data networks operation by understanding wireless and LAN connectivity.

Dec 2015 - Dec 2016 (IT)

First City Monument Bank [FCMB] (Financial institution)

Head Office - 17A Tinubu Street, P O. Box 9117, Lagos.

Network Administration:

- Network Management and integration
- Availability reviews for, LAN/WAN/WLAN, data centres and recovery sites, HQ annexes, branch offices and Offsite-ATM for quarterly reconciliation with providers/vendors.

- Plan, upgrade and maintenance of Cisco equipment on the network, and periodic evaluation for End of Life (EOL)) and End of Support (EOS).
- Ensure the secure integration of all extranet connection to FCMB Network.
- Ensure daily availability and optimization of WAN links and infrastructure to all branches.
- Ensure availability and reliability of LAN infrastructure in the head office and branches.
- Ensure effective monitoring of broadband link for optimized performance.
- Ensure proper configuration and maintenance of all network active devices.
- Ensure the integration of network infrastructure for system services.
- Ensure adequate documentation of network configuration and change management process.
- Ensure proper documentation of network management and System integration.

Processes and Activities

- Assessment of network related incidents/problems with IT Leadership and stakeholders.
- Network Monitoring and Optimization.
- Link Monitoring and optimization 1st Level support
- Troubleshooting network connectivity outages on network active devices 2nd Level Support
- Work with IT officers to resolve link connectivity challenges localized to branches-3rd level support.
- Work with service providers to optimize network links and resolve availability challenges attributed to service providers 4th Level support.
- Monitor and interpret network connectivity challenges using Solarwinds Network Management system (NMS)
- Network traffic analysis to identify network bottlenecks using Solarwinds NMS.
- Providing support, including procedural documentation and relevant reports.
- Users network access control using Forescout and Cisco ISE.
- Manage surveillance teams and vendors for CCTV survey and deployment. Also ensuring security of all DVR/NVR/HVR configuration and footage backup
- Hardening assessment of network devices in data centres, DRC, branches and off sites ATM connections.

Terminals

- Liaising with network provider for link deployment for ATM site
- Configuration of network devices, and integration of new link for ATMs.

- Network Security hardening for ATMs, and POSs using Forescout and Cisco ISE
- Troubleshooting and resolving of all ATMs and POSs network access related issues.
- Manage and maintain all networking, wireless and telephony Solution.

Data Centre Management

• Assist data centres (DC) crew on key regulatory conformance, as well as regular follow up with DC support team towards a sustainable environment reading.

PROFILE

LANGUAGES English & Yoruba

DATE OF BIRTH 8th April, 1994

MARITAL STATUS Single

SEX Male

HOBBIES Music, Sports, Comedy, Surfing Internet, Making Researches.

Travelling and Making New Good Friends.

STATE OF ORIGIN Ekiti State

NATIONALTY Nigerian

PERSONAL ATRIBUTES Ability to take on new responsibilities and work well within a team

environment, Excellent in communication skills, and ability to work effectively in a fast paced implementation environment, Good character, posse's integrity and constant learning and put what has

been learn into good use and ability to multi task.

PROJECTS/PUBICATIONS

2019 CONSTRUCTION AND IMPLEMENTATION OF A TEMPERATURE CONTROLLED FAN

Final Year Project in HND

2015 CONSTRUCTION AND IMPLEMENTATION OF A THREE WAY TRAFFIC LIGHT

Final Year Project in ND

REFEREES

Pelumi BODUNWA

HOD, Core Banking Applications (UNIFIED PAYMENTS)

+234 803 474 2360

pelumini.bodunwa@up-ng.com

Emmanuel Obinna

Head of Engineering, (PLANET FM, UYO)

+2348060248510

emxchi10@gmail.com